We've been waiting for you, Thorn Princess.
Hello.
Your garden is as lovely as ever, Shopkeeper.
It is, isn't it?
By providing water, pruning,
and giving consistent care...
We can ensure that the world
continues to stay beautiful.
Welcome, Thorn Princess.
The heather smells so nice.
The leaves of the spindle tree
also look lovely right now.
Take a look.
Wow!
Goodness, that startled me!
I beg your pardon.
I feared that your skills may have
dulled since you obtained a family...
But it seems you have not changed.
Now I can let you serve our
next customer without worry.
Of course! I am ready to end
any evildoer at any time!
How reassuring. But...
You will be providing
protection on this mission.
Protection?
Plan to Cross the Border
Have you heard of the Gretcher family?
For generations, they have
been a powerful force
that has managed this country's
underworld with honor.
A little while back, the boss and his
two sons were killed due to infighting.
The only ones of the Gretcher
family who survived...
were Olka Gretcher and her son.
She's being kept in a safehouse for now.
But the man who took over their
organization, Leonardo Hapoon,
is desperately trying to find her.
I hear he's put a tremendous
bounty on her head
and every hitman in the country
and beyond is on the move.
We've decided to have her seek
asylum in another country.
Her escape route will be on the sea.
To evade detection by the coast guard,
she will go out to sea on
a normal passenger ship
and then rendezvous with a foreign craft.
I'd like you to stay by her side
until she is safely handed over.
Protecting this mafia person from hitmen...
Of course, it would be ideal if
she doesn't run into the enemy.
But you are there for insurance.
The boss who was killed was a man
I owe a debt of gratitude to,
so I would very much like you to accept.
I see...
Um, but what about my job at city hall?
Also, if I'm going to be
gone for several days,
I have to think up an excuse
to give my family.
You needn't worry about that.
I had a plan concocted so
you could go on this mission
as a part of your job as a civil servant.
Your manager will fill you
in on the details later.
I'm counting on you to
handle this, Thorn Princess.
So that this world can remain beautiful.
A-All right... I'll do my best!
It's been a while since I've had a job.
I must be prepared.
Yuri!
Sis?!
It's rare to see you on this train.
Uh, yeah... I just got back
from a business trip.
Actually, I was arresting
a political criminal.
Well, good work. Would you
like to join us for dinner?
Can I?!
Er, I mean... I'll pass.
Loidy's at your place, and I've
still got some work to do.
Like sorting through audio transcripts.
Goodness, when will you finally
just get along with him?
I won't.
Have you been eating properly?
Make sure you're not leaving
dirty socks lying around.
Sis, I'm not a kid anymore.
Yes...
Yes, of course.
Now stopping at Fogue Square.
I can't keep clinging to you forever.
Fogue Square.
Though I just did the other day...
And actually, you should rely on
me if anything ever happens.
I'll immediately execute Loidy at any time!
See you later.
Sis!
I guess Yuri's all grown up now.
Of course he is.
He now has a proper job and
is making a living on his own.
Little
Brother
He doesn't need my help anymore.
Is there actually any reason why
I should continue my job as a killer?
Too bad! Your seventh-place prize,
one scrubby brush.
Scrubby Brush
Damn it!
Grand Raffle
1 Luxury Cruise
2 Diamond Scrubby Brush
3 Platinum Scrubby Brush
4 Crystal Scrubby Brush
5 Gold Scrubby Brush
6 Premium Scrubby Brush
7 Scrubby Brush
Step right up! Central Mall's
biannual grand raffle is underway!
Every 30 dalc spent gets you one ticket
you can use to test your luck in the raffle!
First prize, believe it or not,
is two tickets for that luxury cruise
everyone's buzzing about lately!
Keep those tries coming!
Papa.
I'm thinking about going on that boat
and having a grand adventure.
I see. How valiant of you.
Now give the hero Anya the raffle ticket.
Just remember, we only have one.
Aw, too bad. Here's your
sixth-place premium scrubby brush.
What the hell, man? Is there even
a ticket in there for first prize?
First place has yet to be claimed!
You fools.
Keep dropping money on a first
prize you're never going to win.
That cruise is going to be mine.
I've made sure of that.
Yeah, yeah, I know. We're
supposed to act like strangers.
The first-place prize ticket is
stuck to the top of the box.
None of you are gonna get it!
Call it a perk of working this job!
Aren't you excited, Cindy?
I don't even like cruises,
but whatever. I guess I'll go if I can.
Aw, too bad! Here's your
fifth-place gold scrubby brush!
Oh? Are you next, little lady?
Here you go. Hope you win!
Go on. Hurry up and pick
a losing ticket, pipsqueak.
The nice lady behind you is
gonna pick the first-place prize.
Wha—
We have a winner!
How?!
I'm home, Loid, Miss Anya.
Mama, hear me!
Luxury Cruise
Anya has won a luxury cruise!
What?!
She managed to win first prize
at a department store's raffle.
My, that's amazing!
Too amazing. It's making me
wonder if it's some sort of trap.
Papa is suspicious of everything.
Since there are two tickets,
why don't you go with her, Yor?
I still have to work.
I'm so excited! I've never been to the ocean!
Borf, borf!
You get to stay home, Bond.
Borf!
The cruise ship Princess Lorelei?
This is the ship I'm going
to be taking for work!
Huh?
And it's the exact ship
that's leaving on Friday...
You're going on a ship for work?
Oh, yes.
Um... the city is trying to attract
a famous department store,
so I'm entertaining someone
very important from there.
Ah, must be a modern form of urban planning.
It's actually a job to protect a very
important client from assassins.
A job battling assassins?!
So if they happen to end
up on the same ship as me,
it might make my job quite difficult.
What should I do?
We can't cause trouble for Mama.
Forget about this ooting.
Who cares?
Anya wants to relax on the big boat.
You're thinking the exact same thing.
You're right.
If we go and help Mama with her work,
we might be killing two
birds with one stone.
Be honest with yourself. You know
you just want to go see the ocean.
Anya wants to go on the
big boat! The big boat!
If I can't, I'm gonna turn bad!
Oh, dear...
Hm... I'll ask my work tomorrow
if I can get paid time off.
Sure, that's fine.
Huh?!
I'll pull some strings so you can
get time off at the hospital, too.
Uh... Thank you very much.
Expectations
Be serious! I'm going to work you
until nothing's left but bones!
HQ may or may not be trying to cut
back on our shady overtime practices.
I see...
Well, little Anya's care and education
are part of Strix, as well.
Agent Twilight,
I order you to perfectly execute
a type of mission called a vacation.
An ooting! An ooting!
Anya hasn't been on an ooting
with Mama and Papa in forever.
Staying Home
It has been a while,
though I'm going for work.
You'll fall out.
If not for this bodyguard job,
the three of us could've enjoyed
this vacation together.
What in the world am I saying?!
That's putting the cart before the horse!
What's the matter, Mama?
Oh, the next station is
where we're getting off.
But maybe...
Maybe if...
this could be my final
job as Thorn Princess...
Ooh!
It's huge!
Excited, excited, excited, excited, excited,
excited, excited, excited, excited, excited!
Calm down.
Well, I have to meet up with my coworkers
from city hall, so I'll see you later.
If it's possible, I will contact you later.
I'm sorry we get to have fun without you.
Mama, do your best!
A pool!
A circus!
A game room!
And...
The ocean!
Papa, this ship is amazing!
I feel a big adventure coming on!
Well, this luxury cruise ship
is Ostania's pride and joy.
Let's hurry and go exploring!
After we put our luggage in our room.
Our own suite! So exciting!
It appears we've accidentally come
to the jail. This place is wrong.
This place is right.
This is what you're gonna
get down in third class.
Please look forward to Anya's grand
adventure in our next feature.
You won this cruise in a raffle.
Don't get greedy now.
But this is Anya's first bunkbed!
Anya's gonna live on top!
Do as you please. Just don't fall off.
Yor and her company are probably
in the first-class rooms.
No fair. Darn celebrities.
Well, they are entertaining guests, so...
Allow us to formally introduce ourselves.
I am Matthew McMahon, director
of policy at Berlint City Hall.
This is Heymann and Vides from
our business development team.
And this is Forger.
I'm Furseal Grey, from the store development
group at Arhaus Department Stores.
This is my wife, Shaty.
I apologize for bringing our child along.
Oh, no! Please, we want you and your
family to enjoy your time here!
If your wife needs any assistance,
Forger will be happy to help in any way.
Thank you.
So this is Ms. Olka from the Gretcher family.
She looks completely
different from her picture.
Did she manage to change her
face to help her escape?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Pleasure.
So this is Ms. Olka's bodyguard?
She seems awfully thin.
Is she really up to this?
This Princess Lorelei
cruise will be a short one.
Three days and two nights,
just visiting the nearby islands.
We hope you'll be able to relax
and enjoy this trip, Mr. Grey.
Though it's no department store,
this ship does have a shopping mall.
Would you like to go take a look?
These two are just normal employees
who don't know the truth, right?
Sure, let's go.
I'm fine. I'll stay here and watch the baby.
I see. Then we will have
Forger stay behind with you.
Right this way, Mr. Grey.
Huh? Um...
Is one bodyguard going to be enough?
Shouldn't we all stay together?
She should be quite safe in her room.
We will first be checking
the rest of the ship.
You needn't worry. She is quite strong.
Your mission this time will be
to protect the sole survivors
of the Gretcher family, Olka and her son.
We've received intel that the one
after her has sent several assassins.
If need be, eliminate the enemies.
I'm counting on you, Thorn Princess.
They checked for possible infiltration
and escape routes before we left,
but I can't relax until I
personally check everything.
I'm sure the manager is also checking, but...
Huh... I guess you really are one of them.
Huh? Uh, yes.
One of who?
Um... You are Miss Olka... Right?
I am. Though I'd prefer that you didn't
call me by that name aboard this ship.
Oh! I'm so sorry!
Oh, did you wake up?
Oh, I'm so terribly sorry!
Mama... Mama...
It's so strange.
I've literally changed my face,
but he still knows that I'm his mother.
I'm sure it's due to my voice, my scent,
and his eyesight not being
fully developed yet.
It is unfortunate that I'll never get
to hear, "He looks just like you."
But that doesn't matter right now.
Besides, he looks like his father,
so it'd turn out the same either way.
Y-Your husband? He seemed
like a lovely person.
The man you just saw is just
a member of our organization.
He's just playing the part.
He is a good man, though.
My husband was killed along
with the rest of my family.
That's why the only one
I have left is my son here.
I'm so sorry, I...
It's fine. You can say this
is a gangster's destiny.
But... I'm a bit tired now.
I don't need the crime family or its money.
I just want to live a quiet, peaceful life.
There, there. What's got you so spooked?
Say, Miss Bodyguard...
Can I be a bit selfish?
Ever since my family was killed,
I've been forced to live in hiding.
I'd like to stretch my
wings just a little bit.
I also want him to be able to
breathe the fresh air outside.
Um... But without the director's permission...
Please. Just for a little bit.
The ones after me don't
know what I look like,
nor should they know that I'm on this ship.
And... you'll protect me if
it comes to that, won't you?
V-Very well.
Just for a little bit.
If you keep acting that suspiciously,
won't you bring more attention to us?
Oh, er... I am being cautious
of the enemy, but, um...
Your family is on this ship?
Yes... My husband and daughter.
Papa! We need to hurry up and
explore the ship before it sinks!
It's not going to sink!
Stop scaring everyone!
But...
This ship certainly is huge.
There seems to be quite a
few celebrities present.
Just in case of a terrorist incident,
I should check for any suspicious people
aboard and confirm the layout of the ship.
I need to figure out which people might
assemble, as well as where and when...
Papa, you're not having fun.
Damn it... My usual habits.
I order you to perfectly execute
a type of mission called a vacation.
I must rest.
I must do my absolute best to enjoy
this vacation to its fullest!
Why don't we go see a show?!
You're so serious, Papa.
Ah...
But why did you bring them with you?
Oh, I didn't. This was all
completely coincidental...
My family doesn't know about my real job.
So if a battle does happen to break out,
it would be very inconvenient
if they were to spot me.
Then again, having any of the other
guests seeing me would be a problem...
Well, if they're in third class,
you probably won't see them
unless we go to a common area.
There's nothing to worry about.
Yes, but...
You seem really worried about this.
That family's just for camouflage, right?
Yes... You're right...
Is... that true?
Oh, right! Let's hurry and step outside!
Oh, wait.
I'll let you borrow this.
It feels so nice.
Um, this outfit...
Now we just look like two mom friends
who came to enjoy the cruise.
It's better than the suit.
And if your husband sees you, he probably
won't recognize you from far away.
Yes, you do have a point.
Ah...
What a nice, peaceful breeze.
Wow... We can't see the shore at all anymore.
You're right.
I left so much behind.
Oh, dear. Are you getting cold?
I guess we can head back.
Um, Shaty!
I'll... I'll do my best!
I'll make sure to protect...
I promise to properly do my job!
Besh! Besh!
Yes, I will do my very besh!
Gram...
Huh?
That's his name. Just like
my father's. His real name.
Dam!
It's a pleasure to meet you, Gram!
Want to hold him as we walk back?
May I?!
I need to do my utmost best
not to break any of his bones!
I'm so sorry! I'll give him back to you, Shaty!
Hey, there's a show at five!
Where's the bathroom?
Let's grab drinks at the bar upstairs.
Wow! You can even go shopping here!
Dad!
What's the matter? Don't stray.
I'm certain you will win the next election...
No, no, those stocks right now are...
Well, this isn't good. The lock to
the emergency passage is broken.
I was almost forced to stay behind.
That's why I told you not to do it.
Shut up! Next time I'll—
This company's products—
This is so good!
So there you have it.
E-226, all clear.
What am I going to do with them?
For real?
Gram...
That's...name. Just like...father's.
It's a...to meet you, Gram!
I'm so sorry! I'll give him back to you, Shaty!
Shaty, Shaty...
Shaty Hutton, room 2125.
Shaty Copeland, room 3064.
Shaty Grey, room 8053.
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
The Fearsome Luxury Cruise Ship